I love the invocation by pastor of one church, Mr. Herb Young.
Let's pray.
I Father, I God, we thank you for this nine.
We pray for those who are in the path of the storms tonight, Lord, that you would keep everyone safe.
We thank you for our city employees, God, the hard work, that they do.
We appreciate that, Lord, we pray for the decisions that are made to nine grand wisdom.
We pray God for the businesses that are already here.
We pray for more businesses that will come that would bring jobs that would pay well.
So families could build their future around them.
We pray that in Jesus name.
Amen.
I pledge to leave this land by the boys and girls club.
To this land.
To the United States of America.
I introduce the re-bobbling for which it stands.
One nation.
Another guy.
I think of this book.
With liberty and justice for all.
Thank you.
Thanks guys.
Oh, thank you.
Hi.
Five.
Six minutes from April 1st, 2024.
Reg room meeting in April 15th.
Reg room meeting.
Motion to crew.
Second.
High.
SB.
Hi.
Lisa.
Seven.
Gillil Stratton Edmund is a poor client for civil litigation in the amount of 5,500 dollars.
Yes.
This is the expert P.
For Dr. Lou.
This special master in the Civil Education Kiss, this is from March 1st to March 31st, 2024.
I've been 300,000, that was approved by the Council on 9 to 2008 for Civil Education
Cross in Bob and GRDA dollars.
It's this, it was a pretty good $450,500 that will leave the balance of $18,893 dollars.
Motion to approve.
Same.
Do you step back Williams?
I'm staying.
All right.
Eight.
Budget amendment number 24.
That's 16.
Right away, we're seeing an expending.
The insurance where you burst into checks to help pay for the replacing.
By the many excavator that was destroyed in the Public Works Garage fire April 2023.
They're going to add some money to this and purchase the excavator to replace that.
This is receiving an expending that the insurance check.
He's got one.
Both.
Most two proof.
Sight.
Sil.
Nine.
Award-new annual uncle, as needed, The Electric Service Contract.
C24-1916.
The HK electric and booting booted for fiscal year 2425 as recommended at best to have
a part of the contract upon this summation.
Of all required contract documents and authorized C-mayor to sign the notice to
proceed.
Aaron Council.
We had the HMK Electric in Booth and Booth was the only two services that submitted this on this.
And you can see across here HMK Electric for each of the categories that are listed in Booth and Booth underneath.
We use, we will choose to use the lower rate companies first, and then when there's a lot of work around the city and everything,
we need another one, then it will go to the next closest bid.
It's the staff recommendation that HK Electric in Booth and Booth and Booth,
but it's accepted and used as needed for the best benefit of the city in HMK.
We have this agreement.
It includes three one-year extensions.
We can re-bid it depending on what happens with the economy and everything we'll have to value.
For our most time is that the contractor price, we use the Piano,
and those are the contractor during the Pernice.
Usually during the Pernice, the Pernice is the most time we've paid the contractor in whatever he sends out.
You know, Tyler, we can request a certain thing.
So sometimes it's that Pernice, and then sometimes it's like the journey in the other contractor.
So like we use H&K now for the holidays, because we're trying to take a lot of our overhead down the ground.
And so like H&K will come do that for us all the time.
We'll be on site.
Jesse, do you remember this?
Yes.
So let's just job a job deal.
I think it's just difficult to do this.
So most likely you're always going to have the contractor pay,
but then it requires more people.
I think that's how it would be.
It's not that way.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I was going to say we got H&K.
Yeah.
Here you go.
Is it a brew?
Second.
Hi.
So go.
Perfect.
Hi.
Thank you.
Ten.
I don't need business, so many of which have been...
That has a resonance that's posting this again.
Blood and staff reports.
Troll, trustee community announcements.
13 adjournment.
Motion.
Okay.
Go.
Five.